{
    "subject": "resource/Battle_of_Pancorbo_(1808)",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Battles_involving_Spain",
    "human_readable": "The Battle of Pancorbo in 1808 is a battle involving Spain.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8870303630828857,
            "question": "Was the Battle of Pancorbo a victory or a defeat for Spain?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7940242290496826,
            "question": "What role did the Battle of Pancorbo play in Spanish history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7784498333930969,
            "question": "What country was involved in the Battle of Pancorbo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7089501023292542,
            "question": "When did the Battle of Pancorbo take place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6586953401565552,
            "question": "Where did the Battle of Pancorbo take place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.612654983997345,
            "question": "Were there any famous individuals involved in the Battle of Pancorbo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5634024143218994,
            "question": "Who were the opposing forces in the Battle of Pancorbo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5168514251708984,
            "question": "What were the potential consequences of the Battle of Pancorbo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5157829523086548,
            "question": "How is the Battle of Pancorbo remembered today?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5142202377319336,
            "question": "Can you name any other battles that occurred around the same time as the Battle of Pancorbo?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Battle of Pancorbo in 1808 is a battle involving Spain.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2336_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How is the Battle of Pancorbo remembered today?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2336_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What were the potential consequences of the Battle of Pancorbo?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2336_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who were the opposing forces in the Battle of Pancorbo?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2336_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2336_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2336_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2336_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2336_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2336_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2336_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2336_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2336_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2336_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2336_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the Battle of Pancorbo that took place in 1808 during the Peninsular War, involving Spanish and French forces. This supports the statement that the Battle of Pancorbo in 1808 is a battle involving Spain."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}